giveitlove.com 2019-12-02

# PRIVACY POLICY – giveitlove

Last modified: December 30, 2018

This Privacy Policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) is designed to explain about the data collection practices used by Give It Love, (“ **Company** ,” “ **us** ,” “ **our** ,” and/or “ **we** ”) when you are using the Internet site that you linked from or **giveitlove.com** (collectively the “ **Website** ”). This Privacy Policy is part of our Terms of Service available at [Terms of Service](http://www.giveitlove.com/terms/) , and it applies to end users who use or access the **Website**. If you are not the end user of the Website, you must reflect this Privacy Policy to your end users and ensure their consent.

**1\. YOUR CONSENT**

BY ACCESSING THIS WEBSITE AND USING OUR  SERVICES, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES.

**2\. MINORS**

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13.

**3\. YOUR INFORMATION**

_TYPE OF INFORMATION, COLLECTION AND USES_.

In order to enable you to use various services on our Website and constantly improve and upgrade it, we may use certain end user’s  information (including cookies and local storage). The followings explain what is end user’s information, and what type of information we use in our Website.

_NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION:_

means information that alone cannot identify you, including data we receive and/or extract from your device upon your using of the Website. At all time, we make sure to extract and store the data in an anonymous and aggregative manner.When using the Website, we collect non-personal information of end users that includes details of your visits to our Website, including operating system, browser type, traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.We also collect device IP address that is allocated by the Internet service provider to identify the country and language; In some jurisdictions and given specific circumstances, IP address may be considered to be personal information when used with other information in an attempt to individually identify users. However, we make no such use in the data we collect, and we make no attempt or effort to personally identify any user. We Encode the IP in a manner that can not be identified.

_PERSONAL INFORMATION:_

means information about you that specifically identifies you or, when combined with other information, can be used to identify you. We do not collect or store any personal information in a manner that can identify you.

_STATISTICAL INFORMATION:_

The information we collect automatically is statistical data and does not include personal information.

_COOKIES AND LOCAL STORAGE_

To enhance your user experience, we use “local storage” or place “cookies” on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about you. You may choose to set Your browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, note that some parts of the Website may not function properly.Local Storage and cookies are small text files that are stored on your browser storage. The Website may use cookies, however, the cookie is not used to identify you or to collect personally identifiable information about you.

_THIRD PARTY DATA COLLECTION AND USE OF COOKIES:_

Third Party collection of information:

  * We do not control third parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However, these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) on the [NAI’s website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). You may go to the Digital [Advertising Alliance site](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) to set advertising preferences for participating companies here. If you are outside of the United States, you may set advertising choices for participating companies here: <http://youronlinechoices.eu/>.

Third Party use of Cookies

  * Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, application providers and analytics service providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with other tracking technologies. We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.
  * We have contracted with Yahoo to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting web traffic, statistics, advertisement ‘click-throughs,’ and/or other activities on our website. No personally identifiable data is transferred to Yahoo by us. Where authorized by us, Yahoo may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. However, if you choose, you may opt out from Yahoo’s collection of such information outside of the Yahoo distribution network, by clicking on the following link: [Opt-Out of interest-based advertising](https://www.verizonmedia.com/policies/in/en/verizonmedia/privacy/controls/index.html)
  * We use a service by Criteo to offer targeted advertising to you. You may deactivate the Criteo Service by following instructions in Criteo’s privacy policy (<http://www.criteo.com/privacy/>).

_WHEN DO WE DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION?_

We only disclose or share your non-public personal information with third parties when we believe doing so is permitted by you and/or authorized by this Privacy Policy, for example: we may share aggregated and session level information with some partners as part of troubleshooting investigations, such as in an attempt to track down malicious mobile redirect advertisements.

_LOCATION OF COLLECTED DATA_

We store your information in protected servers in the United States and other countries and in AWS (amazon)secured servers.

**4\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up ­to ­date active and deliverable e­mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

**5\. CONTACT INFORMATION.**

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at: [contact@giveitlove.com](mailto:contact@giveitlove.com)
